Hello and welcome to Z Business. This is
Priya Vishwa Karma and you are watching
a special segment on brokerage calls.
Well, it's the middle of the trading
week and we will discuss seven
businesses that are keeping analyst
busy. Let's catch all the details. The
first stock on today's list is HDFC
Life. HSBC has maintained its buy rating
on HDFC Life Insurance Company with a
target price of 900 rupees per share.
The second stock on the list is ICICI
Lombard. Jeffre has maintained its buy
rating on ICICI Lombard General
Insurance with an increased target price
of 2,300 rupees per share. Earlier the
target was at 2,170
rupees per share. The third stock on the
list is Newand Labs. Goldman Sachs has
maintained a buy rating on the stock
while increasing its target price by 975
rupees to 15,750
rupees per share. The next stock on the
list is Ola. HSBC has maintained a whole
rating on this stock with an increased
target price of 49 rupees per share.
Earlier the target was at 45 rupees per
share. Next we have DV Laps on the list.
Morgan Stanley has maintained an
overweight rating on this stock with a
target price of 7,185
rupees per share. Next is Tata
Technologies. JP Morgan has maintained
an underweight rating on the Tata Group
stock with a new target of 570 rupees
per share. Earlier the target was at 580
rupees per share. And finally we have
Eternal on the list. Goldman Sex has
maintained its buy rating on the stock
with a target of 330 rupees per share.
Earlier the target was at 315 rupees per
share. Well, that's it in this edition
of brokerage calls. We will see you soon
with another basket of buzzing stocks
that analysts are talking about. Until
then, happy trading and happy investing.